Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) Audiovisual Materials
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Video Materials
  - Institutional Messages and Promotions, 1979-2003
    - [Institutional Messages], U-M Hospitals, ISR, "Death of Wolfe", 1979, 1986, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Half Time Spot: English Compositional Board, 1979, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Rose Bowl Spot, Pre-Gator Bowl Spot, 1979, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Various Half-Time Messages, 1978 1984, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Institutional Messages and Stories, 1977-1983, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Technology Institutional Messages, 1981, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Football Spots, Research for Industry, Building Jobs in Michigan, Music School, 1981, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - University of Michigan Three Institutional Messages, 1982, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - University of Michigan Institute of Gerontology 30-second PSA, July 1982, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Dubs of 3 Half Time Messages, 1983-1984, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Rose Bowl TV PSAs, University of Michigan, U.C.L.A, 1983, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - UM Institutional Messages for Televised Basketball Games, February 1985, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Institutional Messages: Stress Research, Student, Faculty Respect, August 30, 1985, VHS Tape (Box 16)
    - Half Time Messages, 1988 1989, U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - "A Chance to Achieve," Black student recruitment slide show produced by UM News Service for Black Alumni Association, 1988, U-Matic Tape (Box 17)
    - [Institutional Messages] HTM-30, HTM-90, September 9, 1989, U-Matic Tape (Box 17)
    - [Institutional Messages] The University of Michigan "Leaders & Best" 90 second, August 31, 1990, U-Matic Tape (Box 17)
    - "Global Citizenship" Institutional Message, February 26, 1991, U-Matic Tape (Box 17)
    - LS&A Undergraduate PSA Promo Spot, February 26, 1991, U-Matic Tape (Box 17)
    - "Crates" news package and institutional message, March 1992, VHS Tape (Box 17)
    - Big Ten Institutional Messages: "Miller", "Cernan", "Lichtenstein", "Lansing", 1992, VHS Tape (Box 17)
    - Big Ten PSA "Arthur Miller", September 15, 1992, U-Matic Tape (Box 17)
    - Residential College Institutional Message, January 20, 1993, VHS Tape (Box 17)
    - Chinese Xian warriors exhibit at the UM Museum of Art, December 1982, (Betacam Tape (Box 17)
    - WDIV-TV's "Salute to Bo" in Cobo Center, May 6, 1990, (VHS Tape (Box 17)
    - Views of School of Business Administration; mostly NW Entrance; May-June 1990, U-Matic Tape (Box 17)
    - Students on the Diag, East of Graduate Library, May-June 1990, U-Matic Tape (Box 17)
    - UM Helicopter Scenes, UM School of Natural Resources, Tape 1 of 3 January 18, 1991, U-Matic Tape (Box 18)
    - UM Helicopter Scenes, UM School of Natural Resources, Tape 2 of 3 January 18, 1991, U-Matic Tape (Box 18)
    - UM Helicopter Scenes, UM School of Natural Resources, Tape 3 of 3 January 18, 1991, U-Matic Tape (Box 18)
    - University of Michigan Program in Scholarly Research Institutional Message, February, 1991, U-Matic Tape (Box 18)
    - UM researchers announce discovery of the schooner Newell Eddy, sunk in Lake Huron during an 1893 gale. August, 1992, U-Matic Tape (Box 18)
    - Cazzie Russell Presentation, December 11, 1993, VHS Tape (Box 18)
    - Campus Scenes from Roger Sutton Stock, Assembled February 16, 1994 Tape 1 of 2, U-Matic Tape (Box 18)
    - Campus Scenes from Roger Sutton Stock, Assembled February 16, 1994 Tape 2 of 2, U-Matic Tape (Box 18)
    - Institutional message for a TV sports event on the Blue Skies K-12 weather instructional program, January 1994, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - Blue Skies, 1994, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - On the Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP), 1994, U-Matic Tape (Box 18)
    - Institutional message for a TV sports event on the Michigan Mandate, January 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - Institutional message for a TV sports event on Community Service Learning at the UM for a TV sports event, February 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - Institutional message for a TV sports event on Community Service Learning at the UM for a TV sports event, February 1995, VHS Tape (Box 18)
    - UM dance students perform "Dance for the Wave Field" at the dedication of "The Wave Field," an earth sculpture created by Maya Lin, October 6, 1995, VHS Tape (Box 18)
    - Business School T-1, February 14, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - Business School T-2, February 14, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - Business School T-3, February 14, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - Business School T-4, February 14, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - Institutional message for a TV sports event on the arts at UM, February 24, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - Raising the largest and first of 50 bells to the top of Lurie Tower April 18, 1996, VHS Tape (Box 18)
    - Institutional message for a TV sports event on the UM underwater observation robot M-Rover, December, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - News Service Produced profile of the UM Center for research on Learning and Teaching, March 1997, VHS Tape (Box 18)
    - Car crash investigation at Mackinac Bridge using the UM's M-Rover, March 4, 1997, VHS Tape (Box 18)
    - On Professor Johann Borenstein's development of CARMEL (Computer-Aided Robotics for Maintenance, Emergency and Life support), May 2, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 18)
    - "Medicine at Michigan: Celebrating 150 Years of Scholarship and Service," narrated by Mike Wallace, 1999, VHS Tape (Box 18)
    - Summer Aerial Footage of Ann Arbor Campus, 1999, U-Matic Tape (Box 19)
    - U of M Y2K PSA 3 X3, February 29, 2000, VHS Tape (Box 19)
    - "And You Can Quote Me On That", Students with Disabilities at the University of Michigan, 2000, VHS Tape (Box 19)
    - Ford School of Public Policy Naming Ceremonies Tape 1, September 12, 2000, Betacam Tape (Box 19)
    - Ford School of Public Policy Naming Ceremonies Tape 2, September 12, 2000, Betacam Tape (Box 19)
    - Institutional Message on the Arthur Miller Theater, February 5, 2001, Betacam Tape (Box 19)
    - "Celebrate Our Heritage: Burton Tower 1936-2001" ceremony celebrating renovations to the carillon tower, November 9, 2001, VHS Tape (Box 19)
    - Institutional Message on the Arthur Miller Theater, February 5, 2001, Betacam Tape (Box 19)
    - "The Role of Graduate Student Instructors at the University of Michigan," produced by the News Service on behalf of the Center for Research on Learning and Teaching for use during new student orientations, May 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 19)
    - "The Role of Graduate Student Instructors at the University of Michigan," produced by the News Service on behalf of the Center for Research on Learning and Teaching for use during new student orientations, May 2002, VHS Tape (Box 19)
    - Selected Michigan Marching Band performances, 2000-2003, Betacam Tape (Box 19)
    - Aerial [Footage] 1 of 2, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 19)
    - Aerial [Footage] 2 of 2, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 19)
    - The UM School of Dentistry, [Undated], VHS Tape (Box 19)
    - "Child Car Seats" Undated, U-Matic Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs, August 14, 1989, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs Tape 14, October 3, 1989, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs Tape 15, October 3, 1989, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs Tape 16, October 3, 1989, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; Homecoming, October 28, 1989, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; Library Scenes/Winter Footage, February 6, 1990, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; Library Scenes/Winter Footage, February 6, 1990, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; Michigan Alumni Video, January 10, 1991, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; Team Michigan Tape 1, September 18, 1992, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; Team Michigan Tape 2, September 18, 1992, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; Team Michigan Tape 3, September 18, 1992, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; Mr. and Mrs. Fred Lyons, October 3, 1992, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; Mr. and Mrs. Fred Lyons, October 3, 1992, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - U of M Development, Lyons Video, April 23, 1993, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - U of M Development, Lyons Video, May 14, 1993, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Development PSAs; U of M Great Dreams (Japan), Undated, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - Great Dreams Need Great Teachers, Undated, VHS Tape (Box 24)
    - 9/11 in Remembrance Concert, September 11, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 15)
    - 9/11 Concert [at the] Power Center; September 11, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 15)
    - International Center -- Union, September 11, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 15)
    - Interstitials, December 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 15)
    - UM A.A. Dana Building exterior and others, October 26, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 15)
    - Ross School of Business Video, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 15)
    - Women's Hoop and Men's Hoop, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 15)
    - Healthy Abs and Back, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 15)
    - Ford Tape [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 15)
    - Storm; [Storm Water Management at the University of Michigan, Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 15)
  - International Issues and Foreign Studies Lectures, 2000-2005
    The International Issues and Foreign Studies Lectures subseries consists of 29 DVCam tapes dated from 2001-2005. These tapes are lectures featuring University scholars and officials discussing geopolitical events, particularly in the post-9/11 era. Topics include the political situation in the Middle East and the United States' intervention, globalization, and the world economy.
    - After the Fall: Vietnam Plus Twenty-Five, First Panel "American and the World", Welcome: Marty Allen, Lee Bollinger, Introduction: Gerald R. Ford, Moderator, Douglas Brinkley, Panel: Richard Haass, John Marsh, Brent Scowcroft, Lawrence Eagleburger, April 7, 2000, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - After the Fall: Vietnam Plus Twenty-Five, Second Panel "The Presidency", Moderator: Douglas Brinkley, Panel: Robert Dallek, Lou Cannon, Roger Porter, Stephen Hess, April 7, 2000, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - After the Fall: Vietnam Plus Twenty-Five, Third Panel "Politics and the Media", Moderator Bernard Kalb, Panel: Gerald Ford, Eugene McCarthy, James Cannon, Haynes Johnson, Closing Remarks: David Gergen, April 7, 2000, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Terrorism and Globalization; "International Perspectives"; International Institute, University of Michigan, September 18, 2001, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Terrorism and Globalization, Looking Back, Looking Forward September 11, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - India: What Next? September 16, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - "Why Wait For Another Afghanistan?" Catherine Bertini, October 16, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Reporting India, Celia Dugger, November 21, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Covering Permanent War, Part I; Knight-Wallace Fellowship Panel, January 27, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Covering Permanent War Part II; Knight-Wallace Fellowship Panel, January 27, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Venezuela & Chavez: Clashing Visions, March 13, 2003 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Making the UN More Effective in Times of Crisis, Richard Holbrooke, March 21, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - International Implications of the War in Iraq; March 31, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Montek Singh Ahluwalia; Globalization & The Indian Economy, September 8, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - The Impact of Human Rights on the Development of International Law Bruno Simma, September 9, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - The Destruction of Civilization and the Obligations of War, UM 22 Edit, October 8, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - The UN's Role in Conflict Management, Namanga Ngongi, October 9, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Globalization, Trade, and Our Fiscal Morass; Robert Rubin, November 11, 2003 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - "Trade Policy as Development Policy?" James Levinsohn, November 20, 2003 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Cuba's Socioeconomic Situation & Prospects, Carmelo Mesa-Lago, January 21, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Madeleine Albright, March 9, 10, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Putin's Russia, Michael McFaul, February 3, 2005 Michigan TV 2 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Vietnam Symposium, March 2005 Part 1 and 2, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Iraq: How Did It Happen? James Fallows, March 15, 2005 Michigan TV 2 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Charles Vest; Improving U.S. Intelligence, Michigan TV 2 Edit, October 12, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Madeleine Albright (Unedited), [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Saudi Arabia & the US, Panel I, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - Saudi Arabia and the U.S. Panel II, Panel III, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 6)
    - In The Balance, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 6)
  - Lectures and Symposia, 1976-2005
    The Lectures and Symposia subseries consists of 105 tapes of mixed video formats: U-Matic, VHS, and Betacam, dated from 1976 to 2005. Included in this subseries are tapes of lectures by visiting distinguished speakers, such as Mexican President Carlos Salinas de Gortari and Vaclav Havel. It also includes symposia that were held at the UM on varying scholarly topics such as intellectual freedom, the 2003 Iraq War, and Life Sciences and Health.
    - UMTV "Time Capsule: Minds or Eyeballs?" (1976), For the Record, (1974), City Desk: Anonymous Source (1976), DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - NSRP: An Overview, UM Transportation Research Institute, October, 1992, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - Mexican President Carlos Salinas de Gortari delivering the William Simon Lecture, May 27, 1993, VHS Tape (Box 8)
    - Columbia University history Professor Emeritus Walter P. Metzger gives the annual Davis, Markert, Nickerson Lecture, March 21, 1994, U-Matic Tape (Box 8)
    - Mary Stewart, Her First 90 Years, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - William Bridges, Ph.D. "Managing Organizational Transition: A Seminar for Managers and Administrators", 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - William Bridges, Ph.D. "The New World of Work and How to be Successful in It", 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - Amistad; Tape Change Close; January 4, 1998, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - Amistad Facts and Fiction; Panel Discussion with Dr. Patrick Pieh, Dr. Lester Monts, Gail Drakes, and Ahmad A. Rahman, Live Coverage from the Michigan Union, February 4, 1998, U-Matic Tape (Box 8)
    - Amistad Facts and Fiction; Panel Discussion with Dr. Patrick Pieh, Dr. Lester Monts, Gail Drakes, and Ahmad A. Rahman, Live Coverage from the Michigan Union, February 4, 1998 Source Tape 1 of 2, U-Matic Tape (Box 8)
    - Amistad Facts and Fiction; Panel Discussion with Dr. Patrick Pieh, Dr. Lester Monts, Gail Drakes, and Ahmad A. Rahman, Live Coverage from the Michigan Union, February 4, 1998 Source Tape 2 of 2, U-Matic Tape (Box 8)
    - The University of Michigan Hosts the First Lady, April 28, 1998, VHS Tape (Box 8)
    - Bentley Library Marshall Symposium, May 1998, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - Lucas Rakocija "If God Rears His Ugly Head" 1999, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - CHPI #1 Interview, May 7, 1999, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - CHPI #2, May 7, 1999, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - GC; New Student Convocation, September 1999, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Ford School of Public Policy Naming Ceremony and Press Conference, November 18, 1999, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Governor's Conference Video, May 13, 1999, Mini DV Tape (Box 8)
    - Governor's Conference, May 26, 1999, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - Vaclav Havel at UM, honorary degree, symposium, news conference, September 5, 2000, VHS Tape (Box 8)
    - Vaclav Havel at UM, honorary degree, symposium, September 5, 2000, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - Gerald Ford Ceremony, September, 12 2000, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Library "The Making of America" Celebration, Doris Kearns Goodwin, Speaker March 12, 2001, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Wallace House #1, March 21, 2001, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - Wallace House #2, March 21, 2001, Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - Jesse Jackson #1, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 8)
    - Makeup on Empty Space: Andrei Codrescu, January 15, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Kenneth Warner Lecture; Distinguished Faculty, February 6, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - From the UM's Life Science Values and Society Lecture Series, UM pathology Professor Richard Miller: "Are There Genes for Aging?" February 10, 2002, VHS Tape (Box 8)
    - From the UM's Life Science Values and Society Lecture Series, UM pathology Professor Richard Miller on "Extending Human Longevity", February 17, 2002, VHS Tape (Box 8)
    - Makeup on Empty Space: Andrei Codrescu, March 8, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Nancy Cantor Lectureship, Nancy Cantor, September 25, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - "Searching for a Historical Tradition" Romila Thapar, September 27, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - "Of Women & Sons & Lovers" Ralph Williams, October 3, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Seventh Annual Waggoner Lectureship "Care without Coverage" Mary Sue Coleman, October 9, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - MFA Program in Creative Writing 20th Anniversary, October 24, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit TV-MA, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - 12th Annual Davis, Markert, Nickerson Lecture. Catharine MacKinnon, October 31, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Frank Effwageshik, Michigan Union, November 21 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Georgetown University law Professor David Cole presents 13th annual Davis, Markert, Nickerson Lecture on Academic and Intellectual Freedom, October 2, 2003, and VHS Tape (Box 8)
    - Town Hall Meeting, Arthur Levitt, February 4, 2003 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Distinguished University Professor Lawrence Sklar; Dappled Theories in a Uniform World, February 12, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Henry Russell Lecture, March 11, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - The Buck Stops Here, Ford School Panel, September 1, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - 2003 Josh Rosenthal Lecture, Robin Wright, UM 22 Edit, September 8, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - The Food Page Knight-Wallace Panel, September 15, 2003 UM 22 Final Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Engineering Dean's Forum, October 17, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - 13th Annual Davis, Market, Nickerson, Lecture, David Cole, October 20, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Mullin Welch Lecture, Maureen Mahoney, October 26, 2003 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Wallenberg Lecture Bill Brash, October 28, 2003 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Sara's Secrets, Sara Moulton, November 14, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 8)
    - Election 2004 Too Long, Not Nice; the Next Four Years, [2004], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Lani Guinier, January 19, 2004 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Labor and Social Change, Arturo Rodriguez, January 21, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - John Trudell, January 26, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Peter Raven, February 2, 2004 Michigan TV 2 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - University Summit on Campus Climate & Community, Morning Session, Luncheon, Wrap-up, February 11, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - School Desegregation: Long Shadow of Little Rock, Ernest green, February 12, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Rock N' Roll Rebellion, Kora Jackowska, March 5, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - School Desegregation in the 21st Century; March 25, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Wege Lecture, Peter Newman, March 31, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Nancy Cantor Lecture, Claude Steele, April 1, 2004 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Charlayne Hunter-Gault, April 13, 2004 Michigan TV 2 edit, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - 2004 Citigroup Lecture, Dennis Archer, April 14, 2004 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - What Does It All Mean? Theodore Shaw, May 7, 2004 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - American Dream, Jason DeParle, September 28, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Davis, Markert, Nickerson, Lecture, Noam Chomsky, October 28, 2004 Michigan TV 2 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Sheldon Krimsky, November 17, 2004 David J. Gross, November 3, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Howard Markel, December 2, 2004 Patty Gersteinblith, September 30, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - A conversation with Walter Mosley, TRT, taped January 31, 2005 Edited February 8, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Joseph Stiglitz, 2005 Citigroup Lecture, February 15, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Motherhood before Marriage, Kathryn Edin, March 11, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - MSA [Michigan Student Assembly] Debates March 21, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - MSA [Michigan Student Assembly] Debates, March 31, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Carl Levin, Josh Rosenthal Lecture, September 16, 2005 Michigan TV 2 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Sweetland Conference Part I, Michigan TV 2 Edit, September 23, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Sweetland Conference Part II, Michigan TV 2 Edit, September 24, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Sweetland Conference, Part III, Michigan TV 2 Edit, September 24, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Sweetland Conference Part IV; September 24, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - New Orleans: An American Pompeii, Michigan TV Edit, September 29, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Floyd Abrams: Davis, Markert, Nickerson Lecture, October 6, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Helping America's Youth, October 27, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Helping America's Youth Sessions 1, 2, 3, 4, 8, Vid, Michigan TV 2 Edit, October 27, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Helping America's Youth Sessions 5, 6, 7, October 27, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - White House Conference, #1 Dub [Tape inside box says "Research Channel Promo"], [October 27, 2005], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - White House Conference, #1 Dub; [October 27, 2005], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - White House Conference, #2 Dub; [October 27, 2005], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - White House Conference on Helping Youth, October 27, 2005 Tape 3 of 3 [Tape inside box says Replay 2005], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Art: 21, 301, 302, 303; [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Noam Chomsky MiTV 2; Badged [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Robert Mankoff Lectures, I: History, II: Picking [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - E.J. Dionne, Sir Tony, Michigan TV 2 Edit, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - University of Toledo Law; [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - University of Toledo Law; McGovern, Shabtai, Stock Market Crash; [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - The City Desk, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - MSC DC: [Mark Brodsky at the Competitors and Collaborators Conference, Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - The Women of Color Task Force, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Flu; [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Quality Pays Part 1 of 2 [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - Quality Pays Part 2 of 2 [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 9)
    - William Bridges Seminar Part I; [Undated], U-Matic Tape (Box 9)
    - William Bridges Seminar Part II; [Undated], U-Matic Tape (Box 9)
    - University of Michigan, Governors Conference, Graphics Review (W.I.P.), [Undated], U-Matic Tape (Box 9)
    - Continued University Presentation of Research, Psychological Implication Invited Paper, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 9)
    - Continued University Presentation of Research, Psychological Implication Invited Paper, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 9)
    - Continued University Presentation of Research, Psychological Implication Invited Paper, [Undated], Betacam Tape
  - Martin Luther King Junior Memorials and Events, 1998-2006